<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>2024 - Modular Classrooms - TIPS</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>{!Account.Name} can get modular classrooms through TIPS</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi! Do you think {!Account.Name} will need to lease or purchase modular classrooms for the 2024/2025 school year?

BOXX Modular has two competitively won contracts with TIPS USA (The Interlocal Purchasing System) that can help you simplify and accelerate procurement of both temporary and permanent classroom buildings without going out for bid!

{!Account.Name} can both rent and purchase modular buildings through TIPS USA. Since {!Account.Name} is already a member of TIPS USA the bidding legwork has already been done for you.

For your reference, BOXX Modular&apos;s TIPS USA contracts are as follows:
(https://www.tips-usa.com/vendorProfile.cfm?RecordID=51E09B5D3C458F2F374955901EB339B9)

230902 | Permanent Modular Buildings
21020201 &amp; 21020202 | Portable Modular Buildings

You may want to take a moment to view examples of modular classrooms you can procure through our TIPS contracts. https://www.boxxmodular.com/classrooms/

BOXX Modular also offers Modular Office Buildings (https://www.boxxmodular.com/offices/) and Specialty Modular Buildings (https://www.boxxmodular.com/specialty/).



To LEARN MORE or request a quote

&gt; Reply to this email

&gt; Request A Quote on our website (https://boxxmodular.com/quote-request/)

&gt; Call 877-966-7839 to speak with your local expert



About TIPS USA...(https://www.tips-usa.com/)

&gt; TIPS USA contracts are awarded by Region 9 ESC&apos;s board members, a public agency in Texas commissioned by the Texas state legislature and governed by seven board members which are elected by local school board members.

&gt; Vendors, including BOXX Modular, are vetted through a strict competitive procurement process.

&gt; The bidding statute is Chapter 44031 of the Texas Education Code.


BOXX Modular is here to help you get the space {!Account.Name} needs as quickly and easily as possible!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
